TRINH TIEN PHAT

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



https://tienphat-portfolio.vercel.app/



0938.068.917



phattiengg1412@gmail.com



Ba Diem, Hoc Mon, TPHCM

As a Front-End Developer, I'm constantly pushing the boundaries of what's possible in web development. With a strong foundation in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Tailwind, and SCSS, I'm ready to take on any challenge and help create amazing online experiences.

Skillset

- HTML & CSS
- Javascript
- ReactJs
- NextJs
- Redux Toolkit
- SASS
- TailwindCss
- Antd
- ChakraUI
- GSAP
- Team work
- Self study

Education

UNIVERSITY OF TRANSPORT HCM

Auto Mechanics

2017 - 2021

CYBERSOFT ACADEMY

Front-end Course

03/2021 - 10/2021

Language

English - Toeic 650

Certification

ReactJS by TopCV x TestCenter:

https://certificate.testcenter.vn/dk55VTofMlcZNV 9GVjE2bFN7SXU

Team Work by TopCV x TestCenter:

https://certificate.testcenter.vn/dk54UD0fMlcZ NV9GVjE2bFN7SXU

Work Experience

INTERN FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Cong Ty CP CN & KT Stech

08/2022 - 11/2022

Participated in the development of the Dakshow project, focusing on studying and updating the UI and creating new functions.

FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Cong Ty CP CN & KT Stech

11/2022 - present

- Continuously participated in the development of the Dakshow project by creating and optimizing code and enhancing functionality.
- Collaborated with the BE team to create and update APIs.
- Build a core service to manage APIs.
- Contributed to building the company's websites:
 - Stechvn website: https://stechvn.org
 - Welcome Dakshow website: https://welcome.dakshow.com
 - ICO website
 - CMS for Dakshow

PORTFOLIO

Personal project

- My portfolio, wheret you can get more infomation about me.
- Visit page via link: https://tienphat-portfolio.vercel.app/
- Visit repo via link: https://github.com/phattien991412/myportfolio
- Technology: HTML/SASS, Javascript, ReactJs, GSAP, ChakraUI

NETFLIX

Personal project

- A clone UI Netflix
- Feature: Login/Register, Login with Google/Github, Add/Remove movie from list, modal info.
- Visit page via link: https://netflix-clone-47.vercel.app/
- Visit repo via link: https://github.com/phattiengg1412/netflix-clone
- Technology: HTML/CSS, Javascript, ReactJs, NextJs, Next/Auth, TailwinCss, SwiperJs, SWR, Prisma, MongoDB